there's so much text in today's world
当今世界有如此多的文本
pretty much none of us have
我们几乎没人见过
enough time to read all the things we wish
有足够的时间读我们想读的东西
we had time to
我们有时间
so one of the most
所以是最
exciting applications I've seen of large
这是我见过的最令人兴奋的应用
language models is use it
语言模型就是使用它
to summarize text
总结文本
and this is something that I'm seeing
这就是我所看到的
multiple teams built into
多个团队组成
multiple software applications
多种软件应用
you can do this in the Chart GPT web interface
您可以在Chart GPT web界面中执行此操作
I do this all the time to summarise articles
我总是这样总结文章
so I can just kind of
所以我可以
read the content of many more articles than I
阅读的文章比我多得多
previously could
以前可以
and if you want to do this more programmatically
如果你想更程序化地做这个
you'll see how to in this lesson
你会在这节课上看到怎么做
so with that
就讲到这里
let's dig into the code to see how you could
让我们深入研究代码，看看您是如何做到的
use this yourself to summarise text
你自己也可以用这个来总结文章
so let's start off with the same
我们从相同的开始
starter code as you saw before
如前所述的启动代码
of import openai
进口开放
load the API key and here's that get completion
加载API密钥，这是getcompletion
Holper function
帮助功能
I'm going to use as
我用as
a running example
一个正在运行的例子
the task of summarizing this product review
总结本次产品回顾的任务
got this Panda plush toy
我得到了这个熊猫毛绒玩具
from a daughter's
从一个女儿的
birthday who loves it and takes it everywhere
生日的人爱它，带着它到处走
and so on and so on
以此类推
if you're building an e commerce website
如果你正在建立一个电子商务网站
and there's just a large volume of reviews
有大量的评论
having a tool
拥有一个工具
to summarise the lengthy reviews could give you a way
总结冗长的评论可以给你一个方法
to very quickly
很快地
glance over more reviews to get a better sense of what
浏览更多评论以更好地了解内容
all your customers are thinking
你所有的客户都在思考
so here's a prompt for generating a summary
下面是生成摘要的提示符
your task is generally short
你的任务通常很短
some we have a probably review from e commerce website
我们有一些来自电子商务网站的评论
summarize review below
总结如下
and so on in Atmos 30 words
在Atmos 30个单词中等等
and so this is
这就是
Softencupe Panda plush toy loved by daughter a
软毛熊猫毛绒玩具深受女儿a的喜爱
bit smaller than a price arrive early
比价格小一点，早点到
not bad it's a pretty good summary
不错，这是一个很好的总结
and as you saw in the previous video
正如你在之前的视频中看到的
you can also play with things like
你也可以玩一些东西，比如
controlling the character count
控制字符数
or the number of sentences
或者句子的数量
to affect the length of this summary
来影响摘要的长度
now
现在
sometimes when creating a summary if you have a very
有时在创建摘要时，如果你有一个非常
specific purpose in mind for the summary
具体目的为头脑总结
for example if you want to give feedback
例如，如果你想给予反馈
to the shipping department
给船务部门
you can also modify the prompt
您也可以修改提示符
to reflect that
为了反映这一点
so that they can generate a summary that is
这样他们就可以生成一个总结
more applicable
更适用的
to one particularly group in your business
在你的业务中有一个特别的群体
so for example if I add
例如，如果我加上
to give
给
feedback
反馈
to the
到
shipping department
运输部门
let's say I changed this too start to focus on
假设我也改变了这个开始关注
any aspects that I mentioned
我提到的任何方面
shipping and delivery of the product
产品的运输和交付
and if I run this then
如果我运行这个
again you get a summary
你会得到一个总结
but instead of starting off with
而不是从
Softing Cupanda plush toy
柔软的熊猫毛绒玩具
it now focuses on the fact that it arrived a day
它现在关注的是它到达了一天的事实
earlier
早些时候
than expected and then the store has you know
比预期的要多，然后商店就有
other details then
其他细节
or as another example if we aren't
或者作为另一个例子，如果我们不是
trying to give feedback to the shipping department
试着给船务部门反馈
but let's say we want to give feedback
但是假设我们想要给出反馈
to the pricing department
给定价部门
so the pricing department is
所以定价部门
responsible determining the price of the product
负责确定产品的价格
and
和
I'm going to tell it to focus on
我要让它专注于
any aspects
任何方面
they're relevant to the price and perceive value
它们与价格和感知价值相关
then just generates a different summary
然后生成一个不同的摘要
that it says maybe the price may be too high for a size
它说，对于一个尺码来说，价格可能太高了
now in the some reads that I've
在我读过的一些文章中
generated for the shipping department or the
为运输部门或
pricing department it
定价部
focus a bit more on information relevant
更多地关注相关信息
to those specific departments
具体到这些部门
and in fact feel free to pause the video now and
现在可以暂停视频了
maybe ask it to generate information for
也许让它生成信息
the product department responsible for the cosmic
负责宇宙产品的部门
experience of the product
产品体验
or for something else that you think
或者其他你认为的东西
might be interesting to an
我可能会感兴趣
e commerce site
电子商务网站
but in these summaries
但是在这些总结中
even though it generated the information
即使它产生了信息
relevant to shipping it had
与航运相关
some other information too which you could decide
还有一些你可以决定的信息
may or may not be helpful
可能有用，也可能没用
so
所以
depending on how you want to summarise it you can also
根据你想如何总结，你也可以
ask it to extract information rather than summarize it
要求它提取信息而不是总结信息
so here's a prompt that says
这里有一个提示
Utah's extract relevant information
犹他州提取相关信息
to give feedback to shipping department and now
给船务部门和现在的反馈
it just says probably arrived a day earlier
上面只说可能提前一天到达
than expected
比预期的
without all of the
没有所有的
other information
其他信息
which was also hopeful in the general summary but
这在总结性总结中也是有希望的，但是
less specific to the
不太具体
shipping department
运输部门
if all I wanted to know is
如果我只想知道
what happened with the shipping
运输出什么事了
lastly let me just share of you a concrete example
最后，我想给大家举一个具体的例子
for how to use this in a workflow to help
对于如何在工作流中使用它有所帮助
summarize multiple reviews
总结多个评论
to make them easier to read
to make them easier to read
so
so
here are a few reviews this is kind of long but
这里有一些评论，有点长，但是
here's the second review for a standing lamp
这是对一盏立灯的第二篇评论
need a lamp from a bedroom
需要一盏卧室的灯
here's a third review for an electric toothbrush
这是对电动牙刷的第三条评论
my dental hygienist recommended
我的牙齿保健师推荐的
kind of a long review about a electric tube brush
这是一篇关于电子管刷的长篇评论
this is a review for a blender when it's at so set 17
这是对搅拌器的回顾，当它在17档时
pieces to someone seasonal sale and so on and so on
把零碎的东西给别人季节性出售等等
this is actually a lot of texts
这实际上是很多文本
if you want feel free to pause the video
如果你想的话可以暂停视频
and read through all this text
通读这篇文章
but one of you want to know what these
但你们有人想知道这些是什么
reviewers wrotes without having to
评论者不用写就写
stop and read all this in detail
停下来仔细阅读这一切
so I'm going to set review 1
所以我将复习设为1
to be just the product review that we had up there
就像我们在上面做的产品评论一样
and I'm gonna put all of these reviews into a list
我要把这些评论整理成一张清单
and now if I implement a
现在如果我实现a
full loop over the reviews
完整的评论循环
so here's my prompt
这是我的提示
and here I've asked it to summarise it in at most
这里我要求它最多总结一下
20 words then let's have it
20个单词，就这么定了
get the response and print it out and let's run that
获取响应并打印出来，然后运行它
and it prints out
然后打印出来
the first review is that Panda toy review
第一条评论是关于熊猫玩具的评论
some really review of the lamp
一些真正的评论灯
some review of the toothbrush and then the blender
对牙刷和搅拌器做一些评价
and so if you have
如果你有
websites where you have
在这些网站上
hundreds of reviews you can imagine
数以百计的评论，你可以想象
how you might use this to build a dashboard to take
如何使用它来构建一个仪表板
huge numbers of reviews
大量的评论
generate summaries of them so that
generate summaries of them so that
you or someone else can browse the reviews much more
你或其他人可以浏览更多的评论
quickly and then if they wish maybe click in
很快，如果他们愿意，可以点击进去
to see the original longer review and this can help you
要看原版较长的复习，这对你有帮助
efficiently get a better sense of what
有效地获得更好的感觉
all of your customers are thinking
你所有的客户都在思考
alright
好吧
so that's it for summarizing and I hope that you can
这就是总结，我希望你们能
picture
图片
if you have any applications with many pieces of text
如果您的应用程序有许多文本片段
how you can use
如何使用
prompts like these to summarize them to help people
像这样的提示来总结它们以帮助人们
quickly get a sense of what's in the text
快速了解文章内容
the many pieces of text
许多文本
and perhaps optionally dig in more if they wish
如果他们愿意，可能还会有选择地多吃一些
in the next video
下个视频中
we'll look at
我们来看看
another capability of lash language models
语言模型的另一个功能
which is to make inferences
哪一个是推论
using text for example
以文本为例
whether you had
你是否有
a game product reviews and you wanted to very quickly
一个游戏产品的评论，你想要非常迅速
get a sense of
了解…
which product reviews have a positive or negative
哪些产品评论是正面的，哪些是负面的
sentiment
情绪
let's take a look at how to do that in the next video
下个视频我们来看看怎么做